[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Традиційна культура' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "でんとうぶんか"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'розваги' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ごらく"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Чайна церемонія' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'чай' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おちゃ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'шлях' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みち"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Каліграфія' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кабукі' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かぶき"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Театр Но' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のう"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Театр Бунраку' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぶんらく"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сумо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すもう"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Дзюдо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅうどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кендо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Карате' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "からて"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まんざい"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "らくご"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ґо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いご"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сьоги' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ігровий автомат' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "パチンコ"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the word 'Танець на фестиваль “Бон”' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぼんおどり"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the word 'Танець' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おどり"
    }
]